<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Story>

	<!--[Warmup & introducing chapters]-->
	<Chapter0>
		<ChapterInfo> Normal </ChapterInfo>
		<Lines>
			<Line>[Narrator] While you’re sleeping you remember the day when you met your friend ten years ago.</Line>
			<Line>[Narrator] You got separated from your mother while shopping at the market. Trying to find your mother back you encountered a young girl about the same age as you.</Line>
			<Line>[Narrator] Curiously you got closer to the girl who seemed frightened upon seeing you.</Line>
			<Line>[Rose] Hello, who are you? I’m Rose.</Line>
			<Line>[Mya] M…..Mya..</Line>
			<Line>[Rose] Did you also separate from your mother? Don’t be scared, we will find our mothers together.</Line>
			<Line>[Mya] Mother doesn’t want Mya. Mother doesn't wake up anymore.</Line>
			<Line>[Rose] W- what about your father?</Line>
			<Line>[Narrator] Mya shud her head as if to say she didn't have a father.</Line>
			<Line>[Rose] Then how about you come with me? Our house is big, I’m sure mother and father wouldn't mind.</Line>
			<Line>[Narrator] Mya hesitated for a while but in the end grabbed the hand you reached out.</Line>
			<Line>[Narrator] ...</Line>
			<Line>[Narrator] Meanwhile you're smiling as you’re dreaming about the past, your father already long gotten up and left for work….</Line>
			<Line>[BlackScreen, 1]</Line>
		</Lines>
		<Options>
			<Option1>
				<Text>
					<OptionText> [Anykey] </OptionText>
					<AfterText> [@] </AfterText>
				</Text>
				<Points>0</Points>
				<NextChapter>Chapter1</NextChapter>
				<ButtonId>0</ButtonId>
			</Option1>
		</Options>
	</Chapter0>
	<Chapter0b>
		<ChapterInfo> Normal </ChapterInfo>
		<Lines>
			<Line>[Narrator] While you’re sleeping you remember the day when you met your friend ten years ago.</Line>
			<Line>[Narrator] You got separated from your mother while shopping at the market. Trying to find your mother back you encountered a young girl about the same age as you.</Line>
			<Line>[Narrator] Curiously you got closer to the girl who seemed frightened upon seeing you.</Line>
			<Line>[Rose] Hello, who are you? I’m Rose.</Line>
			<Line>[Mya] ...</Line>

			<Line>[mya]	I.. don’t remember..</Line>
			<Line>[Rose]Then how about I’ll find a name for you.</Line>
			<Line>How about …[inputfield]……..</Line>
			<Line>[input accepted]Yes ill be … [input denied]No…. just call me Myu instead…</Line>

			<Line>[Rose] Did you also separate from your mother? Don’t be scared, we will find our mothers together.</Line>
			<Line>[Mya] Mother doesn’t want Mya. Mother doesn't wake up anymore.</Line>
			<Line>[Rose] W- what about your father?</Line>
			<Line>[Narrator] Mya shud her head as if to say she didn't have a father.</Line>
			<Line>[Rose] Then how about you come with me? Our house is big, I’m sure mother and father wouldn't mind.</Line>
			<Line>[Narrator] Mya hesitated for a while but in the end grabbed the hand you reached out.</Line>
			<Line>[Narrator] ...</Line>
			<Line>[Narrator] Meanwhile you're smiling as you’re dreaming about the past, your father already long gotten up and left for work….</Line>
			<Line>[BlackScreen, 1]</Line>
		</Lines>
		<Options>
			<Option1>
				<Text>
					<OptionText> [Anykey] </OptionText>
					<AfterText> [@] </AfterText>
				</Text>
				<Points>0</Points>
				<NextChapter>Chapter1</NextChapter>
				<ButtonId>0</ButtonId>
			</Option1>
		</Options>
	</Chapter0b>

	<!--[Prelude chapters]-->
	<Chapter1>
		<ChapterInfo> Normal </ChapterInfo>
		<Lines>
			<Line>[Emperor] How dare you?!</Line>
			<Line>[Emperor]	Your mistake took the lives of many people! And why, only because of your greed?!</Line>
			<Line>[Narrator] The emperor is enraged at the official who made a grave mistake in attempts for a promotion and his pride.</Line>
			<Line>[Narrator] The official, already kneeling, bends over even further, shivering in fear.</Line>
			<Line>[Father] P- please forgive me, your majesty. Please have mercy.</Line>
			<Line>[Emperor] Silence! Your mistake can only be accounted for with your head!</Line>
			<Line>[Emperor] Actually.. Not even your head will satisfy me to relieve my anger!</Line>
			<Line>[Father] Your majesty, I beg you.</Line>
			<Line>[Narrator] The emperor slams his hand on the table with a loud bang and sweeps off a few cups and plates which break right away.</Line>
			<Line>[Narrator] Hearing the slam and broken plates, the eunuchs guarding the door shiver in fear. Whenever the emperor is displeased, they are the ones who have to deal with the afterblow.</Line>
			<Line>[Narrator] Suddenly the head eunuch in the room hides a small smile and walks up to the emperor to whisper in his ear. The emperor smiles as he looks at the official.</Line>
			<Line>[Emperor] So… you want a chance to pay for your mistake? I heard you still have an unmarried beautiful daughter.</Line>
			<Line>[Father] Y-yes, your majesty.</Line>		
			<Line>[Narrator] In surprise and relief the official relaxes his bow and raises slightly.</Line>
			<Line>[Father] M-my eldest daughter is just about the right age to get married. If your majesty is interested, I can send her off to you.</Line>
			<Line>[Emperor] If I’m interested? If I am interested?! I’m not interested in your brat!</Line>
			<Line>[Narrator] The official looks confused at the emperor and carefully asks.</Line>
			<Line>[Father] N-not interested? T-then what about her?</Line>
			<Line>[Narrator] The emperor smiles.</Line>
			<Line>[Emperor] General Stone is still looking for a wife. Marry your daughter to him and I’ll forgive you.</Line>
			<Line>[Father] (G-General Stone...? Liam Stone..? The brute who kills without a second thought? I can't do this to Rose..)</Line>
			<Line>[Narrator] In shock, the official bows all the way down to the ground again.</Line>
			<Line>[Father] P-P-Please y-your m-m-majesty. Anyone but h-him.</Line>
			<Line>[Emperor] THIS ISN'T A SUGGESTION, THIS IS AN ORDER!</Line>
			<Line>[Father] Y-Your majesty...</Line>
			<Line>[Emperor] You may choose, marry her off to the general, or grant me the heads of your whole clan.</Line>
			<Line>[Father] B-but, your majesty.. I-I fear h-he might not like her.</Line>
			<Line>[Emperor] If general Stone isn't interested, he may do with her as he pleases. She's at his disposal now, I don't care.</Line>		
			<Line>[Emperor] Now get the fuck out of here!</Line>
			<Line>[Narrator] The official shivers in regret. His begging caused him to involve his family. Understanding he can not push the emperor any further, he gives up.</Line>
			<Line>[Father] I- I.. I understand..</Line>
			<Line>[BlackScreen, 1]</Line>
		</Lines>
		<Options>
			<Option1>
				<Text>
					<OptionText> [Anykey] </OptionText>
					<AfterText> [@] </AfterText>
				</Text>
				<Points>0</Points>
				<NextChapter>Chapter2</NextChapter>
				<ButtonId>0</ButtonId>
			</Option1>
		</Options>
	</Chapter1>
	<Chapter2>
		<ChapterInfo> Normal </ChapterInfo>
		<Lines>
			<Line>[Mya] Rose...? Rose...?! Where are you hiding this time?</Line>
			<Line>[Rose] Boo! Hahaha.</Line>
			<Line>[Narrator] Rose jumps out of the storage box with a big smile on her face.</Line>
			<Line>[Mya] Rose…</Line>
			<Line>[Mya] You’re too old for this! Your mother would be really displeased if she knew.</Line>
			<Line>[Rose] But it’s just you and you wouldn’t tell anyone.</Line>
			<Line>[Narrator] Rose smiles as Mya looks around and sees the items on the ground which belong in the box Rose just jumped out of. Mya sighs and places the items back.</Line>
			<Line>[Mya] Of course I won't tell anyone! I’m your personal maid and childhood friend. But if your parents find out, I’m the one in trouble for not stopping you.</Line>
			<Line>[Narrator] Rose grabs Mya’s hands and smiles as a way of saying she won’t let anyone hurt her.</Line>

			<Line>[Rose] Actually…. Tonight I dreamed of the time we met…</Line>
			<Line>[Rose] Do you still remember?</Line>
			<Line>[Narrator] Mya looks up in surprise and smiles gently.</Line>
			<Line>[Mya] I do, I probably wouldn't have survived if not for that day…</Line>
			<Line>[Mya] Your father wasn’t too pleased when you asked if I could stay.</Line>
			<Line>[Rose] Until you offered to be my maid and promised to work hard. And you sure did work hard.</Line>
			<Line>[Mya] Yeah.. aside from my chores you forced me to play with you too.</Line>
			<Line>[Rose] Now don't say you didn't enjoy that.</Line>
			<Line>[Narrator] Mya laughs at Rose's pouting face.</Line>
			<Line>[Mya] I did enjoy that. As busy as I was, I always enjoyed fooling around with you and getting into trouble together.</Line>
			<Line>[Narrator] Both Mya and Rose start to laugh as they remember the past.</Line>

			<Line>[Mya] Rose, if you are done playing around, you should practice serving tea. You don't want to embarrass yourself in front of your husband when you're married.</Line>
			<Line>[Rose] Don't worry about that, there's still a lot of time left before I get married. I don’t think my parents are looking for a husband yet.</Line>
			<Line>[Mya] They probably feel embarrassed with your behaviour…</Line>
			<Line>[Mya] Even if they aren't looking yet, you should still practice for when the time comes.</Line>
		</Lines>
		<Options>
			<Option1>
				<Text>
					<OptionText>Practice serving tea</OptionText>
					<AfterText>[Rose] Fine.. I’ll practice properly so you don't have to keep worrying about it.</AfterText>
				</Text>
				<Points>0</Points>
				<NextChapter>Puzzle:Tea</NextChapter>
				<ButtonId>0</ButtonId>
			</Option1>
			<Option2>
				<Text>
					<OptionText>Go to the garden </OptionText>
					<AfterText>[Rose] I will do it tomorrow.. The weather is so nice today, let's go to the garden.</AfterText>
				</Text>
				<Points>0</Points>
				<NextChapter>Chapter:Garden</NextChapter>
				<ButtonId>1</ButtonId>
			</Option2>
		</Options>
	</Chapter2>
	<ChapterGarden>
		<ChapterInfo> Normal </ChapterInfo>
		<Lines>
			<Line>[Narrator] Mya agreed and the two went to the garden.</Line>
			<Line>[Narrator] Rose and Mya walk around the beautiful flowers enjoying their sweet scents. Suddenly Rose saw a butterfly and got an idea.</Line>
			<Line>[Rose] Lets catch some butterflies!</Line>
		</Lines>
		<Options>
			<Option1>
				<Text>
					<OptionText>Practice serving tea</OptionText>
					<AfterText>[Rose] Fine.. I’ll practice properly so you don't have to keep worrying about it.</AfterText>
				</Text>
				<Points>0</Points>
				<NextChapter>Puzzle:Garden</NextChapter>
				<ButtonId>0</ButtonId>
			</Option1>
		</Options>
	</ChapterGarden>

	<Chapter3>
		<ChapterInfo> Normal </ChapterInfo>
		<Lines>
			<Line>[Narrator]Another maid ran up to Rose and Mya with a worried look on her face.</Line>
			<Line>[Maid]Miss! Your father is looking for you and he seemed quite unhappy! Did you do anything again?</Line>
			<Line>[Narrator]Rose and Mya look at eachother.</Line>
			<Line>[Rose]I didn't do anything today…. I think…?</Line>
			<Line>[Mya]… Are you giving trouble now without even realizing it? Come let's go to your father before he gets more upset.</Line>
			<Line>[Narrator]Rose and Mya follow the other maid to Rose's father.</Line>
			<Line>[Narrator]When they arrive they see how both Rose’s parents are waiting. Rose’s father seems quite sad while her mother is in tears.</Line>
			<Line>[Narrator]Rose quietly walks up to them.</Line>
			<Line>[Rose]What's wrong..?</Line>
			<Line>[Narrator]Upon seeing Rose, her mother starts to cry even louder. She gets up to walk to Rose and hugs her.</Line>
			<Line>[Mother]Is there really no other way?</Line>
			<Line>[Narrator]Rose’s father shakes his head slowly. Rose stares confused at the two.</Line>
			<Line>[Rose]Mother? Father? What happened?</Line>
			<Line>[Father]Rose…. I’m so sorry…</Line>
			<Line>[Narrator]Rose her father hesitates for a bit before he continues. Unsure how to break the news to her.</Line>
			<Line>[Father]The emperor has ordered for you to marry the general…</Line>
			<Line>[Rose]Marrying a general? Isn't that good news?</Line>
			<Line>[Narrator]Rose asks hesitantly.</Line>
			<Line>[Father]You have to marry general Stone..</Line>
			<Line>[Father]Rumours say hes…</Line>
			<Line>[Narrator]Rose tries to recognize the name as she couldn't remember where she heard it before.</Line>
			<Line>[Father]He’s quite a brute..</Line>
			<Line>[Father]You will be in danger if you marry him…</Line>
			<Line>[Mother]Why did it have to be our child.. Why Rose..</Line>
			<Line>[Narrator]Rose couldn't believe what she's hearing.</Line>
			<Line>[Rose]Why..?! Why do I have to marry a bute?! Why me?!</Line>
			<Line>[Father]I made a mistake and this is the punishment the emperor chose. There's nothing I can do, I can't refuse an imperial edict.</Line>
		</Lines>
		<Options>
			<Option1>
				<Text>
					<OptionText>I understand... </OptionText>
					<AfterText>[Rose] I understand… Don’t worry father… </AfterText>
				</Text>
				<Points>0</Points>
				<NextChapter>Chapter4a</NextChapter>
				<ButtonId>0</ButtonId>
			</Option1>
			<Option2>
				<Text>
					<OptionText>No! I wont accept this! </OptionText>
					<AfterText>[Rose] No! I wont accept this! This is your fault! Why do I have to pay for it?!</AfterText>
				</Text>
				<Points>0</Points>
				<NextChapter>Chapter4b</NextChapter>
				<ButtonId>1</ButtonId>
			</Option2>
		</Options>
	</Chapter3>
	<Chapter4a>
		<ChapterInfo> Normal </ChapterInfo>
		<Lines>
			<Line>[Narrator] Rose closes her eyes and takes a deep breath</Line>
			<Line>[Rose] If there's no choice, I’ll marry him.</Line>
			<Line>[Rose] Maybe things won't turn out as bad as they seem.</Line>
			<Line>[Narrator] Rose returns to her room. She sits down on her bed quietly.</Line>
			<Line>[Rose] Since that man is dangerous, I’ll have to be careful..</Line>
			<Line>[Rose] Should I make him love me? Should I make him send me away?</Line>
			<Line>[Rose] Destiny is in my hands now.</Line>
		</Lines>
		<Options>
			<Option1>
				<Text>
					<OptionText> [Anykey] </OptionText>
					<AfterText> [@] </AfterText>
				</Text>
				<Points>0</Points>
				<NextChapter> .. </NextChapter>
				<ButtonId>0</ButtonId>
			</Option1>
		</Options>
	</Chapter4a>
	<Chapter4b>
		<ChapterInfo> Normal </ChapterInfo>
		<Lines>
			<Line>[Narrator] Rose gets mad and raises her voice.</Line>
			<Line>[Rose] It’s unfair! UNFAIR!!</Line>
			<Line>[Mother] Rose..</Line>
			<Line>[Rose] No!</Line>
			<Line>[Rose] I won’t marry!</Line>
			<Line>[Narrator] Rose’s father who felt sad and guilty before suddenly gets angry at her behaviour</Line>
			<Line>[Father] Rose! You have no choice! You will marry him!</Line>
			<Line>[Father] If I could decline, I wouldn't marry you to such a man. But we can't decline! You hear me?!</Line>
			<Line>[Father] It’s either that or all of our heads..</Line>
			<Line>[Rose] I don't care! I hate you!</Line>
			<Line>[Narrator] Rose screams and cries before running out.</Line>
			<Line>[Narrator] Rose runs to her room and drops in tears on her bed.</Line>
			<Line>[Rose] If I really have to marry that guy…</Line>
			<Line>[Rose] I will take destiny in my own hands… Lets see if he still wants me..</Line>
		</Lines>
		<Options>
			<Option1>
				<Text>
					<OptionText> [Anykey] </OptionText>
					<AfterText> [@] </AfterText>
				</Text>
				<Points>0</Points>
				<NextChapter> .. </NextChapter>
				<ButtonId>0</ButtonId>
			</Option1>
		</Options>
	</Chapter4b>


	<!--Endings-->
	<!--Chapter Template
	<Chapter..>
		<ChapterInfo> Normal </ChapterInfo>
		<Lines>
			<Line></Line>
			<Line></Line>
			<Line></Line>
		</Lines>
		<Options>
			<Option1>
				<Text>					
					<OptionText> .. </OptionText>
					<AfterText> [@] </AfterText>
				</Text>
				<Points>0</Points>
				<NextChapter>Chapter..</NextChapter>
				<ButtonId>0</ButtonId>
			</Option1>
			<Option2>
				<Text>
					<OptionText> .. </OptionText>
					<AfterText> [@] </AfterText>
				</Text>
				<Points>0</Points>
				<NextChapter>Chapter..</NextChapter>
				<ButtonId>1</ButtonId>
			</Option2>
		</Options>
	</Chapter..>
	-->
</Story>